Alizé DEBRAY

Front-end developer & business analyst

Objective

Whether commercial or technical, my professional experiences are all linked by a subject that deeply animates me: the user experience. My goal is to put the vast knowledge gained in this field at the service of an innovative company, by participating in the creation of ergonomic and profitable interfaces.

Experience

Business analyst at Amadeus

Nice, France | Mai 2018 - Present

Amadeus is the world's leading provider of distribution solutions for the travel and tourism industry.

 Designed features to enhance an existing web application based on customer needs

Front-end developer at The New Luncher

Singapore | December 2016 - April 2017

The New Luncher is a start-up that allows parents to order lunch boxes for their children at school.

- Participated in the launch of the start-up
- Conceived an online user experience in line with the brand image
- Designed and developed an AngularJS web application

Front-end development intern at SeeChic

Singapore | Mai 2016 - December 2016

SeeChic is a start-up that sells contact lenses and sunglasses online.

- Participated in the redesign of a website in its entirety
- Enhanced an online user experience to increase conversion rate
- Designed and developed the front-end of a web interface
- Managed the production of content

Salesperson at IKEA

Lille, France | October 2015 - December 2015

IKEA is the largest furniture retailer in the world.

- Advised clients on home textiles
- Took care of customer journey in my area

Front-end development intern at Orange

Lille, France | June 2015 – August 2015

Orange is the French leader in telecommunications.

- Helped improve the administration of business clients by internal users
- Developed the front-end of a web application

Software development volunteer at Com&Web

Lille, France | April 2015 – August 2015

Com&Web is a charity that sells websites and communication materials to raise funds for disadvantaged people.

 Designed and developed showcase websites to attract potential clients for small businesses

Sales intern at Darty

Paris, France | July 2014 - August 2014

Darty is the leading French chain of home appliance stores.

- Pursued a training in sales methods
- Advised clients on small appliances
- Took care of the customer journey in my area

Mystery customer at Orphée

Paris, France | Mai 2013 - September 2013

Orphée is a company specializing in the evaluation of the user experience.

- Evaluated the customer service of one of the leading French car dealers

Tel.: +33(0)676670504

Email: contact@alizedebray.com

Skype ID: alizedebray

Education

Iteem, Centrale Lille

2013 -2018

Master's degree in industrial and entrepreneurial engineering.

Skema Business School

2017 - 2018

Master's degree in project and program management & business development.

Certifications

PRINCE2® Foundation AgilePM® Foundation GPM-B®

Languages

French Mother tongue
English Advanced (C1)
Spanish Intermediate (B1)

Technical skills

Bootstrap Sass jQuery Angular Python Django

Soft skills

Ambitious Resourceful Inquisitive Innovative

Interests

Health Sustainability Crafts

References

Souad-Marie Assaad

Technical Specialist at Google Tel.: +65 8650 3827

Email: souad.eudes@gmail.com

Fabrice Demarest

Project manager at Orange Tel.: +33(0)328390071

Email: fabrice.demarest@orange.com